We have the one
My love for you is not
It is the first one that
In the interest of safety
Parents were advised to carry children and children and that
I love to play excavators
Why is
To say
An enemy has been sla
With what stands for
And i think that i know all about the
As
A
Oh
I don't
I like this this time
So the
You have
And has to
It is to see sixty six
How is that a place called numero
Both those can find him visited by the
And so
They could make those together
One two
Yeah
Very very
You meet in the center
How much cost like
When you do do that
Do do that
And we only have one my water
So
On behalf of the whole crew
Welcome on board this show
I say
Created on this march
Like down for san francisco
On board the b a two a five
It was like that
So that the of the time one of the jetties
Uh
Was not working out
Therefore we had to put everyone through the front forward door
But everyone's here now
And we will speak to edge of control and get underway
Ladies and gentlemen
I won't be long before
We depart now for san francisco
Do please check again that you have your seatbelts
Secu
We love you on our journey together to san francisco
A special welcome to those of you returning from our executive club today
And also to those of you joining us from one of our one world alliance partners
A member of the crew
I divide you down to sit back
Relax
Make yourselves at home
Enjoy our hospitality
If there's anything that any of the team can do to make your journey more comfortable
Do please
Let us know
Thank you
Summer
That's right
You were a little place which
Okay
I drive
And make this
Try to just bring it up
Once we have the science fish shop
We will
Of course
Need to ask that you return to your seats
And at that time the toilets were are not gonna be available
But this time so
It's a nice actually get to see it
Thank you
It's not very
Because new mexico
It's almost like a trip to the middle east
Despite the those ancient cultures
Don't open
You love
And you know it
I don't want to
I will put the
We got three
We have some flavor
In the case of the level
He seems to the
But this was the
I don't worry about it
You guys
Good time enough to want to the alerted by the
On the way
Oh my i was like on my tattoo
Though that's pretty
I mean
In my life
So much for you
Yeah
We're doing good
We're really doing this part
I
After the water
Like
I get off
Ha ha ha ha ha like so
Don't care
This is like a powerful
It's just please be careful
Oh my god
Oh
I can't
Oh yeah
Okay
Oh
What
Are the best of the
You know
One thirty four
When you start to
I love you
If you
You know
I have